wwbw.com 2019-05-29

# Support Center: My Privacy

**WOODWIND & BRASSWIND PRIVACY POLICY**

Last Revised: July 17, 2018 

This Woodwind & Brasswind Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") applies to the website located at www.wwbw.com, and any other websites or mobile application owned and operated by Woodwind & Brasswind that direct the viewer or user to this Privacy Policy as well as other communications with Woodwind & Brasswind as identified in this Privacy Policy. Collectively, we refer to www.wwbw.com, and any other website or mobile application owned or operated by Woodwind & Brasswind which refers its users to this Privacy Policy as the "Site." In this Privacy Policy, the terms "Woodwind & Brasswind," "we," "our," and "us" refer to Woodwind & Brasswind, Inc. This Privacy Policy gives you details of our privacy practices, including: (a) what types of information we collect about you; (b) how the information will be used; (c) to whom we disclose the information; and (d) how we safeguard the information. 

**Your Consent**

By using the Site or providing personal information to us through our customer service department in connection with our products or Site or via email or text in response to a Woodwind & Brasswind solicitation or communication, you are agreeing to allow Woodwind & Brasswind to collect and use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. By using the Site you are also agreeing to our Terms of Use. 

**What Information Does Woodwind & Brasswind Collect and Why?**

_Information You Voluntarily Give Us:_

We may ask or allow you to provide us with personal information on a voluntary basis when you call, email or text us or use certain areas of the Site, and you will be required to provide personal information when you make purchases on the Site. The kinds of personal information that we may request may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, email address, telephone number, fax number and credit card information (collectively, "Personal Information"). All such information will be treated in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

You may be required to register and create an account ("Account") to use certain areas of our Site. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Account and are responsible for any activities that occur under your Account. 

In order to access some of the features of the Site, you must be signed in to your Account. You may also be able to sign in to the Site by using your social media log-in information. If you sign in through a social media service, we may collect the information in your profile that you have allowed the social media service to share with us. 

_IP Addresses and "Cookie" Information:_

As is the case with many websites, the Site logs your IP address and uses standard technology called "cookies," which are small data files that are downloaded onto your computer when you use the Site. Cookies automatically identify your browser to the wwbw.com server whenever you interact with the Site. We use cookies and the information they provide to improve the Site and the quality of your experience with the Site. We do not link IP addresses to your name, email address or other Personal Information. Certain kinds of cookies allow us to store your information to save you time in filling out forms on the Site. We only send this type of cookie to your browser when you have provided your consent for us to save your profile information. 

_Web Beacons, Clear GIFs, and Other Technologies:_

The Site may also use "web beacons," "clear GIFs," or other technologies to obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses the Site or when you are provided the opportunity to complete surveys, participate in a sweepstakes or other incentives related to the Site, or when you open or respond to any newsletter or other email you may have received from Woodwind & Brasswind. These technologies may also be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy. These technologies may allow us to track your interaction with the Site from all of your devices, including personal computers, mobile devices, and/or tablets. Such cross-device tracking allows us to serve you with relevant advertisements on the most appropriate device. 

_Information from Third Parties:_

Woodwind & Brasswind may obtain additional information from third parties and add it to information we have collected from you. 

**How Does Woodwind & Brasswind Use Your Information?**

Woodwind & Brasswind may use Personal Information and other information collected automatically for a variety of purposes, including, without limitation, to: 

  * provide you with the requested services or respond to your inquiries;
  * facilitate your purchase(s) on the Site;
  * conduct surveys, sweepstakes, contests, or other special promotions;
  * monitor consumer interest in our products and services;
  * troubleshoot problems that may arise on the Site;
  * protect against fraud or other criminal activity on the Site and other websites;
  * customize your user experience on the Site;
  * notify you of product or service offerings that we think may be of interest to you;
  * assist us in tailoring our product lines, service offerings and the content of the Site to our customers' needs;
  * improve the accuracy of our customer database;
  * increase our understanding of our customer database;
  * increase our understanding of our customers;
  * identify potential new customers; and
  * tailor our advertising to our customers.

To assist in these purposes, at certain times, we create a profile relating to you in order to show you the content that we think you might be interested in and to display the content according to your preferences. 

_Third-Party Optimization Providers:_

We contract with one or more online partners to help manage and optimize our Site and communications. We use the services of one or more marketing companies to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use the Site. To do this, we use web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing companies on the Site. The type of information we collect includes information provided by the customer (including information necessary to complete transactions), IP addresses, cookie information (and other information that tracks browsing and purchasing history). By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from the Site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. 

**How Does Woodwind & Brasswind Share Information?**

_Service Providers:_

Woodwind & Brasswind may disclose Personal Information about individual users to third parties who provide services to Woodwind & Brasswind and who agree to maintain the confidentiality of such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. These third parties provide a variety of services to Woodwind & Brasswind, including, without limitation, fulfilling product orders, managing or hosting the Site, helping create new content and promotions for the Site and sending or coordinating the sending of marketing communications to pre-identified users. In situations where you have supplied your information in connection with a question or request for information about a product or service offered by one of our business partners, we may also send the information you have supplied to the business partner(s) that offer such products or services. 

_Third-Party Advertisers:_

We may share your Personal Information, including, without limitation, your name, address and email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on the Site or offline with us, with third-party advertising partners and their service providers in order to deliver to you banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. 

_As Required by Law:_

Woodwind & Brasswind may be required to share Personal Information in response to a valid court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. In addition, we may share certain Personal Information when we believe that doing so is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of our company and/or others. 

_Subsidiaries and Affiliated Companies/Corporate Change:_

Woodwind & Brasswind may also share Personal Information with controlling entities, entities it controls, and entities under common control. Finally, Woodwind & Brasswind may transfer Personal Information to participating companies in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event. 

_Aggregate/Anonymous Sharing:_

We may also share information we collect about you, your devices and other visitors to the Site in an anonymous or aggregated form with our business partners and others without restriction. 

**Access to Information**

You can correct factual errors in your Personal Information by sending us a request that credibly shows any error. If you wish to access, update or correct your Personal Information that we collect through the Site, please contact us by mail at the address shown in the How to Contact section below. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**Your Choices**

_Email Opt Out:_

From time to time, Woodwind & Brasswind may notify you by email of special promotions, changes to the Site, new product lines or products or service offerings that we think may be of special interest to you. If you decide you no longer want to receive emails notifying you of this information, click here to unsubscribe, or follow the instructions in the promotional message. Email Opt Out requests will be processed within ten (10) days. 

_Postal Mailing List:_

Woodwind & Brasswind may occasionally share its postal mailing list or a part of its mailing list with other organizations. If you do not want your name and address shared with other organizations, or do not wish to receive our mailings, please contact us at [800.348.5003](tel:18003485003). 

Please note that requested changes to our postal mailing list may take up to eight (8) weeks to take effect. 

_Cookies:_

If you prefer not to allow us to use "cookies" to collect information, you can disable the cookies by turning them off in your browser, although some areas of the Site may not function properly if you do. 

_Advertising Opt Out:_

To learn more about the use of your information for advertising or to choose not to have your information used by our third-party advertising partners by opting out, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking here. 

**Do Not Track**

At this time, the Site do not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include "do not track" instructions. However, you may be able to change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser, as described above. We do not knowingly permit third parties to collect Personal Information about your online activities over time and across different web sites and apps when you use the Site. 

**Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use these procedures to better safeguard your information. 

Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as required and only authorized individuals are permitted access to the information that you provide to us. We take physical, technical and administrative measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of Personal Information; however, we cannot guarantee that these measures will prevent breaches of the integrity and security of our network and systems, or that Personal Information will never be accessed or acquired by unauthorized persons, notwithstanding the safeguards we have in place. 

**Links to Third Party Websites**

The Site provides links to various websites operated by third parties including, but not limited to, third party sites that display the Woodwind & Brasswind trademarks. This Privacy Policy does not apply to third party websites that are accessible through the Woodwind & Brasswind Site, unless such website directs users or visitors to this Privacy Policy. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred out of the Site and connected to the website of the organization or company that maintains that website. Even if an affiliation exists between the Site and a third party website, we exercise no control over linked websites. Each of these linked websites maintains its own independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those other websites to learn how they collect, use, share and secure your information before providing any Personal Information. 

**Terms and Modifications to Privacy Policy**

By using the Site, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the Site. Woodwind & Brasswind may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. 

When we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above. If a material change is made to this Privacy Policy, we will post notice of that change on the first page of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your consent to any changes to this Privacy Policy. 

**Collection of Children's Personal Information**

The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13, and Woodwind & Brasswind does not collect or maintain Personal Information online from children we actually know at the time of collection are under the age of 13. Should we discover that we have collected Personal Information online from a child who is under 13, we will promptly delete that Personal Information. If you have concerns over the collection of children's Personal Information on the Site, please contact us at the address in the How to Contact section below. 

**How to Contact**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy and/or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Woodwind & Brasswind, Inc.  
PO Box 7479  
Westlake Village, CA 91359  
Attention: Legal Department  
Phone: [800.348.5003](tel:18003485003)  
Email us using this link

If you communicate with us, we may retain your correspondence to improve our products, services, and the Site, and for other disclosed purposes. We may use information you provide to us in order to send you updates, such as notifications of changes to the terms of our services or important information about our services and products. 

As mentioned below, Woodwind & Brasswind is a participating member of the CARU Safe Harbor Program. If you believe that we have not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact CARU at: 

CARU Safe Harbor  
Attn: Director  
112 Madison Avenue, 3rd Floor  
New York, NY 10016  

**CARU Safe Harbor**

This privacy policy and the CARU icon shown on our websites confirm that Woodwind & Brasswind is a valid licensee and participating member in the CARU Safe Harbor Program ("CARU Safe Harbor"). To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative. CARU has reviewed and certified that we meet established online information collection and use practices on all Woodwind & Brasswind properties where this privacy policy is posted. 

As part of the CARU Safe Harbor, we are subject to audits and frequent monitoring of our websites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by CARU. If you believe that we have not responded to your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact CARU at: 

CARU Safe Harbor  
Attn: Director  
112 Madison Avenue, 3rd Floor  
New York, NY 10016  

**California Privacy Rights**

Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Except as provided herein, or otherwise disclosed to you, we do not share our customer's personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. For inquiries regarding our disclosure policy, please send us an email us using this link, or write us at: Woodwind & Brasswind, Inc., PO Box 7479, Westlake Village, CA 91359. Attention: Legal Department - Privacy. We will be happy to honor your request.
